

.Net Consultant seeking roles in Software Development, Requirements

Analysis, Coding, Unit Testing, Application

UI, Axure, Agile, entity framework

Current Designation: .Net Consultant Total Experience: 5 Year(s) 7 Month(s)

Current Company: Genisys Group Highest Degree: B.Tech/B.E. [Computer Science]

Current Location: Bengaluru / Bangalore Pref. Location: Bengaluru / Bangalore

Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Maintenance

Role: Software Developer

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Marital Status: Single/unmarried

Key Skills: .Net Consultant, Team Lead/Tech Lead, Software Development, Requirements Analysis, Coding, Unit

Testing, Application

Maintenance, Debugging, Asp. Net, C#, OOPS, MVC, ReactJS, JQuery, JavaScript, Bootstrap, CSS, HTML, Ajax, XAF, Kendo

UI, Axure, Agile, entity framework

Verified: Phone Number | Email - id

Last Active: 22-Jan-21 Last Modified: 22-Jan-21

Summary

*5 Years advanced knowledge of ".Net" Software Engineer with expertise in all aspects of the software development life cycle, including Requirements Analysis, design, development and production support.

*Dedicated to constantly improving tools and infrastructure to maximize productivity, minimize system downtime and quickly respond to the changing needs of the business.

Work Experience

Genisys Group as .Net Consultant

Jan 2019 to Till Date

Working as dot net consultant here I'm responsible for development work.

SLK Software (India) Pvt. Ltd. as Software Engineer

Oct 2016 to Dec 2018

- * Working as full stack developer, responsible for requirement gathering to deployment.
- * Learnt new technologies as customer need and assists the team on same.
- Researched, designed and implemented scalable applications.

Gateway Technolabs Pvt. Ltd. as Software Developer

Mar 2015 to Sep 2016

Worked as we b developer and was responsible for development and UAT deployment. Directed software design and development while remaining focused on client needs.

Education

UG: B.Tech/B.E. (Computer Science) from rajasthan technical university, kota in 2013

Other Qualifications/Certifications/Programs:

.Net Programming from Mapple Edusoft Pvt. Ltd.

IT Skills

Skill Name	Version	Last Used	Experience
Asp.Net, C#, OOPS,MVC			
Web API, Core 2.1, XAF, Kendo UI			
ReactJS, JQuery, JavaScript, Web service			
MySQL, Oracle, Entity Framework			
Bootstrap, CSS, Html , Ajax, C, C++			
Visual studio, MS code, Axure-wireframe			
Team Foundation Server, SVN, Git			
JIRA			

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English	Expert			
Hindi	Expert			

Affirmative Action

Physically Challenged: No

Work Authorization

Countries: India

Job Type: Permanent

Employment Status: Full time